Finding Aid for Industrial Works (Bay City, Mich.) records, 1924-1927
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Industrial Works (Bay City, Mich.) records 1924-1927
Industrial Works (Bay City, Mich.).
1 microfilm reel
8575 Bb.2 Microcopy
Bay City, Michigan manufacturing firm; miscellaneous business papers.
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
The records were made available for microfilming by Mrs. Paul Baker (donor no. 4044 ).
No further additions to the records are expected.
The record group is open to research.
The Industrial Works of Bay City, Michigan was a firm which manufactured locomotive cranes.
The record group includes a history, financial material, and correspondence. Most of the correspondence concerning merger with McMyler-Interstate Co. of Cleveland, Ohio.
Subjects:
Industrial Works (Bay City, Mich.); McMyler-Interstate Company; Industries--Michigan--Bay City; Cranes, derricks, etc.; Industries--Ohio--Cleveland; Bay City (Mich.)
- Organizational records
  - History of Industrial Works, 1873-1903 (Reel 1)
  - Financial information, 1913-1924 (Reel 1)
  - Indentures, 1924 (Reel 1)
  - By-laws (Reel 1)
  - Correspondence
    - April 1924 (Reel 1)
    - May-July 1924 (Reel 1)
    - August 1924 (Reel 1)
    - September-October 1924 (Reel 1)
    - 1926-1927 (Reel 1)
  - Miscellanea (Reel 1)